Guide to the New York State Board of Mediation Cases 1952-1964
New York State Board of Mediation Cases
- ARB 2519 - ARB 2852 (1956). (Box 78)
  - ARB-2621 Beegee Transportation, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 36)
  - ARB-2628 Allied Maintenance, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 37)
  - ARB-2630 Amherst Upholstery Co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 38)
  - ARB-2633 Pioneer Ice Cream, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 39)
  - ARB-2634 Brillo Mfg. Co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 40)
  - ARB-2636 Micron Machine Corp., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 41)
  - ARB-2637 Leitner Truck Rental Co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 42)
  - ARB-2639 The King Corporation, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 43)
  - ARB-2644 Riteway Decorators, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 44)
  - ARB-2646 Inwood Oil Terminal, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 45)
  - ARB-2647 Mercury Brush Mfrs. And Marco Brush Co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 46)
  - ARB-2649 Pioneer Ice Cream, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 47)
  - ARB-2650 Manco Watch Strap Mfg. Co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 48)
  - ARB-2651 American Metal Spinning & Stamping Co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 49)
  - ARB-2652 A. N. Plastics, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 50)
  - ARB-2656 J.F.D. Manufacturing Co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 51)
  - ARB-2657 Century Auto Welding & Repair Co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 52)
  - ARB-2661 John Reber Paking, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 53)
  - ARB-2665 Beverly Frame & Moulding Co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 54)
  - ARB-2687 825 Walton Avenue and 828 Gerard Avenue, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 55)
  - ARB-2689 Burner Service Corp., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 56)
  - ARB-2691 The Virginian, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 57)
  - ARB-2696 Flight Foods, Inc., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 58)
  - ARB-2703 Herman Bellman Co., Inc., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 59)
  - ARB-2704 Paul Furman d/b/a Kingston Brush Mfg. Co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 60)
  - ARB-2707 War Baking Co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 61)
  - ARB-2711 Red Rope Stationery, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 62)
  - ARB-2712 Aywon Wire & Metal Co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 63)
  - ARB-2714 Ludwig Baumann Co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 64)
  - ARB-2717 P. Schneider, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 65)
  - ARB-2720-3 Island Art. Inc. Et Al., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 66)
  - ARB-2737 Karlson & Reed, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 67)
  - ARB-2738 Duracold, Inc., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 68)
  - ARB-2748 National Exhibition Co. stat, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 69)
  - ARB-2752 Empire Bias Ending, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 70)
  - ARB-2753 Kendor Oldsmobile, Inc., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 71)
  - ARB-2755 Active Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 72)
  - ARB-2760 George Bayer Chevrolet, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 73)
  - ARB-2761 Sonny Contracting, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 74)
  - ARB-2763 D. Steinberg, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 75)
  - ARB-2767 West Side T.V. Co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 76)
  - ARB-2773 Dee Bee Products Co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 77)
  - ARB-2774 Grand Union Equipment Co., Inc., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 78)
  - ARB-2775 Rose Embroidery Corp., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 79)
  - ARB-2778 X-L Brass Mfg. Company, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 80)
  - ARB-2785 A. Hoffman, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 81)
  - ARB-2787 Certified Upholstery Co., Inc., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 82)
  - ARB-2788 Master Spring Corporation, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 83)
  - ARB-2789 Layton Furniture, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 84)
  - ARB-2791 Jay Dee Interior Decorator, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 85)
  - ARB-2792 Central Upholstery Co., Inc., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 86)
  - ARB-2794 Janet Rosenblum Co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 87)
  - ARB-2797 Digby's Inc., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 88)
  - ARB-2798 Hudson Chromium Co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 89)
  - ARB-2800 Embassy Steel Products, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 90)
  - ARB-2801 Helen Wire Mfg. Corp., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 91)
  - ARB-2802 Parker-Stearns Co., Inc., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 92)
  - ARB-2803 Stanley Equipment Corp., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 93)
  - ARB-2804 Louis Rosenberg, Inc., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 94)
  - ARB-2805 All Style Upholsterers Inc., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 95)
  - ARB-2806 Tifford Furniture Company, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 96)
  - ARB-2807 Columbian Surgical Instrument, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 97)
  - ARB-2808 Belmont Parlor Frame co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 98)
  - ARB-2809 Cabinet Craftsmen Inc., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 99)
  - ARB-2810 Comfort Furniture Frame, Inc., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 100)
  - ARB-2812 S & K Furniture Co., Inc., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 101)
  - ARB-2813 Interboro Furniture Co., Inc., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 102)
  - ARB-2816 3505 - 94th St.) 3508 - 95th St.), 1956 (Box 78, Folder 103)
  - ARB-2819 Mechanical Steel Tubing Corp., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 104)
  - ARB-2822 Elk Trading Company, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 105)
  - ARB-2824 Parkside Demolishers, Inc., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 106)
  - ARB-2825 Trocchio Carting Co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 107)
  - ARB-2828 B & W Novelty, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 108)
  - ARB-2830 Rosenstock Oldsmobile, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 109)
  - ARB-2831 Columbia Surgical Co., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 110)
  - ARB-2832 Parade Motors, Inc., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 111)
  - ARB-2834 Acme Quilting Co., Inc., 1956-1957 (Box 78, Folder 112)
  - ARB-2836 Joint Trade Board of Painters in Nassau county, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 113)
  - ARB-2838 North American Iron & Steel, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 114)
  - ARB-2841 - ARB-2852 Sunshine Upholstery Co. et al., 1956 (Box 78, Folder 115)
- ARB 2853 - ARB 3229 (1956). (Box 79)
  - ARB-2855 Greer Hydraulics, Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - ARB-2856 Manhattan Office Equipment Co., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - ARB-2857 Paddy's Clam House, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - ARB-2859 Dorest Rex Products Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - ARB-2862 American Duro Fastener co., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - ARB-2864 Long Life Spring co., 1956-1957 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - ARB-2866 Duracold, Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - ARB-2869 Joseph Galkin Company, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - ARB-2870 Frey Machine & Motor co., 1957 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - ARB-2872 Unique Headboard Co., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - ARB-2873 Highland Amusement Company, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - ARB-2876 Hyklas Food Products, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - ARB-2877 Piser & Co., Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - ARB-2878 Robin Sportswear Co., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - ARB-28847 Mohawk Business Machines, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - ARB-2891 Metropolitan Sand & Gravel, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - ARB-2894 Mechanical Steel Tubing, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - ARB-2896 Gem Window Cleaning co., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - ARB-2096 Premier Metal Products, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - ARB-2910 Chelsea Desk Co., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - ARB-2911 Towne Delicatessen, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - ARB-2912 2601 Henry Hudson Parkway, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - ARB-2915 Hy & Artie, 1956-1957 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - ARB-2917 Whale Steel Equipment, 1957 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - ARB-2918 441 Ocean Avenue, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - ARB-2963 Automatic Range Co., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - ARB-2965 - ARB-2976 Louis Decorators et Al., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - ARB-2977 Electronic Wiring Corp., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - ARB-2978 1034-38 Tiffany Street, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - ARB-2980 Staley Elevator Corp., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - ARB-2981 Wolf's Sportswear, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - ARB-2982 Associated Amusement Machine Operators of N.Y., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - ARB-2986 Mechanical Steel Tubing, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - ARB-2988 Perfex Products Corp., 1957 (Box 79, Folder 34)
  - ARB-2991 Whitelawn Dairies, Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 35)
  - ARB-2992 2116 Ditmas Ave. Brooklyn, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 36)
  - ARB-2995 Spinner Super Market, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 37)
  - ARB-2996 Wagner Baking Corp., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 38)
  - ARB-2997 Weatherall Products, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 39)
  - ARB-2999 Planet Service Corp., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 40)
  - ARB-3000 Flour Truckmen, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 41)
  - ARB-3006 Kendor Oldsmobile, Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 42)
  - ARB-3007 Progressive Restaurant Owners Assn., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 43)
  - ARB-3009 Atlantic Packard Auto Corp., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 44)
  - ARB-3011 M. H. Harris Optical Co. ARB-3012 Union Square Optical Service, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 45)
  - ARB-3014 Fisher-Stevens, Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 46)
  - ARB-3015 Fisher-Stevens, Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 47)
  - ARB-3018 Master Pharmacy, Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 48)
  - ARB-3024 Radio Wire Television Corp., 1957 (Box 79, Folder 49)
  - ARB-3029 Westinghouse Appliance Sales Corp., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 50)
  - ARB-3030 Silverite Co., Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 51)
  - ARB-3033 Stevens Metal Products Corp., 1956-1957 (Box 79, Folder 52)
  - ARB-3034 - ARB-3039 Louis Decorators et al., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 53)
  - ARB-3042 Drago Stores, Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 54)
  - ARB-3047 Sternberger Motor Corp., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 55)
  - ARB-3048 Eagle Electric Mfg., Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 56)
  - ARB-3051 Greer Hydraulics, Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 57)
  - ARB-3054 Lifton, Gold & Asher, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 58)
  - ARB-3057 Tom Brown's Restaurant, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 59)
  - ARB-3061 Atlantic Gummed Paper Corp., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 60)
  - ARB-3062 Greer Hydraulics, Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 61)
  - ARB-3063 I. Golden Corp., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 62)
  - ARB-3064 Bee Line, Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 63)
  - ARB-3070 S. B. Thomas, Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 64)
  - ARB-3072 Empire phonograph, 1957 (Box 79, Folder 65)
  - ARB-3074 Sanford Tanning Corp., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 66)
  - ARB-3076 Delmand Mfg. Co., Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 67)
  - ARB-3077 Timely Service, Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 68)
  - ARB-3078 Kendor Oldsmobile, 1957 (Box 79, Folder 69)
  - ARB-3081 N. Y. Metal Moulding co., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 70)
  - ARB-3082 I. Krosney & Co., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 71)
  - ARB-3084 Breyer Ice Cream, Co., Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 72)
  - ARB-3087 - ARB-3090 Lehmann Optical Co. et al., 1956-1959 (Box 79, Folder 73)
  - ARB-3092 Ford Instrument Co., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 74)
  - ARB-3097 University Chevrolet, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 75)
  - ARB-3109 Composer Restaurant, 1956-1957 (Box 79, Folder 76)
  - ARB-3117 Rexart Metal, 1956-1957 (Box 79, Folder 77)
  - ARB-3122 Karl Karish & Sons, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 78)
  - ARB-3123 thru ARB-3130 All-Style Upholsterers Inc. et al., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 79)
  - ARB-3131 Dale Drugs, 1957 (Box 79, Folder 80)
  - ARB-3132 Crown Drug Stores, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 81)
  - ARB-3134 Sheek Beauty Salon, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 82)
  - ARB-3146 Gregor Confections Mfg. Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 83)
  - ARB-3147 Gem Window Cleaning Co., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 84)
  - ARB-3149 946-52 Sherman Avenue, 1956-1957 (Box 79, Folder 85)
  - ARB-3159 Lord Optical Company, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 86)
  - ARB-3162 Olympia Provision & Baking, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 87)
  - ARB-3169 Simons Furniture Co., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 88)
  - ARB-3170 Grotty Mfg. Corp., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 89)
  - ARB-3175 Brillo Mfg. Company, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 90)
  - ARB-3177 Moulding Corp. of America, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 91)
  - ARB-3181 Emil Koudelka, Inc., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 92)
  - ARB-3184 769 St. Marks Avenue, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 93)
  - ARB-3186 Embassy Grocery, 1956-1957 (Box 79, Folder 94)
  - ARB-3187 Berkman Bros., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 95)
  - ARB-3194 Sanitary Dash Corp., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 96)
  - ARB-3198 1344-48 St. Nicholas Ave., 1957 (Box 79, Folder 97)
  - ARB-3202 Fisher-Stevens, Inc., 1956-1957 (Box 79, Folder 98)
  - ARB-3203 Al Blader, 1956-1957 (Box 79, Folder 99)
  - ARB-3205 Metropolis Metal Spinning & Stamping Co., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 100)
  - ARB-3210 Sunset Stores (Mamaroneck TV), 1956 (Box 79, Folder 101)
  - ARB-3211 - ARB-3214 Haber Upholstery Shop et al., 1956 (Box 79, Folder 102)
  - ARB-3215 - ARB-3225 I. Axelrod et al., 1957 (Box 79, Folder 103)
  - ARB-3226 Brenner Metal Products, 1956-1957 (Box 79, Folder 104)
  - ARB-3227 Hamburg Heaven, 1956-1957 (Box 79, Folder 105)
  - ARB-3229 International Appliance Co., 1956-1957 (Box 79, Folder 106)
- ARB 3240 - ARB 3518 (1957). (Box 80)
  - ARB-3240 National Gypsum Co., 1956 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - ARB-3243 American News Co., 1956 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - ARB-3244 Victory Maintenance, 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - ARB-3246 1745 Fulton Avenue, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - ARB-3249 Greer Hydraulic, Inc., 1956 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - ARB-3250 Motor Hearse & Car Owners Assn., 1956 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - ARB-3251 H. A. Johnson, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - ARB-3253 Coil Winders, Inc., 1956 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - ARB-3254 Continental Curtain Co., 1956 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - ARB-3258 Recine Way Restaurant, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - ARB-3259 Re-Ly-On Metal Products, Inc., 1956 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - ARB-3263 Dryden Press, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - ARB-3264 Firestone Tire & Rubber, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - ARB-3265 Messing Bakeries, Inc., 1956 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - ARB-3266 Sperry Gyroscope, 1957-1958 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - ARB-3268 570-78 West 193rd Street, 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - ARB-3271 Service Warehouse Co., Inc., 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - ARB-3274 - ARB-3283 Comfort Built Upholstery Co. et Al., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - ARB-3284 Nu-Site Optical Co., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - ARB-3239 Helleige, Inc., 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - ARB-3290 Iso-Sol Company, 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - ARB-3298 Fine Art Pillow & Specialties Co., 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - ARB-3300 126A West 127th Street 145 West 127th Street, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - ARB-3304 300 West 154th Street, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - ARB-3314 Spiral Binding Co., 1956 (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - ARB-3326 New York Spool Co., 1956 (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - ARB-3329 Telectro Industries Corp., 1956 (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - ARB-3330 Mack Markowitz Oldsmobile, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - ARB-3331 Associated Amusement Machine Operators of N.Y., 1955-1957 (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - ARB-3333 Cortile Restaurant, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - ARB-3334 Globe Engineering & Repair Co., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - ARB-3335 Hamburg Heaven, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - ARB-3337 National Sleep Products, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 33)
  - ARB3348 Foamland U.S.A. & Nu Era Wood Products, Inc., 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 34)
  - ARB-3349 Standard Building Products Co., 1956 (Box 80, Folder 35)
  - ARB-3350 Anchor Slide Fastener Corp., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 36)
  - ARB-3353 Iodice Carting Co., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 37)
  - ARB-3355 Kay Manufacturing Corp., 1956 (Box 80, Folder 38)
  - ARB-3356 Fairmount Iron Works Inc., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 39)
  - ARB-3359 Metropolitan Tobacco Co., 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 40)
  - ARB-3363 Hamburg Heaven, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 41)
  - ARB-336 Potato Service Co of New York, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 42)
  - ARB-3369 Newport Optical Mfg. Co., 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 43)
  - ARB-3373 Baron Oldsmobile, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 44)
  - ARB-3377 Kendor Oldsmobile, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 45)
  - ARB-3378 U.S. Plywood, 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 46)
  - ARB-3387 Metropolitan Plywood Distributors Assn., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 47)
  - ARB-3388 Pargament-Filder, Inc., 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 48)
  - ARB-3396 - ARB-3403 ALBA Decorators et al., 1956 (Box 80, Folder 49)
  - ARB-3408 Electrical Insulation Co., Inc., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 50)
  - ARB-3409 National Piano Corporation, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 51)
  - ARB-3416 Q-Line Mfg. Corp., 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 52)
  - ARB-3417 Spartan Shower Stall Co., Inc., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 53)
  - ARB-3421 Franklin Simon & Co. Oppenheim Collins, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 54)
  - ARB-3426 Greer Hydraulics, Inc. (Shop Unit), 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 55)
  - ARB-3427 Greer Hydraulics, Inc., 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 56)
  - ARB-3428 Krug Baking Co., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 57)
  - ARB-3429 K. Polishook & Son, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 58)
  - ARB-3430 Tri-Boro Pontiac Corp., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 59)
  - ARB-3435 Federal Screen & Sash Co., 1956 (Box 80, Folder 60)
  - ARB-3443 Rexart Metal Industries, Inc., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 61)
  - ARB-3445 Green Construction Co., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 62)
  - ARB-3450 1155 Simpson Street, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 63)
  - ARB-3451 1224 Walton Avenue, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 64)
  - ARB-3452 Albro Metal Products Corp., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 65)
  - ARB-3454 Sweet's Restaurant, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 66)
  - ARB-3455 Leone's Restaurant, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 67)
  - ARB-3456 Polskin Bros., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 68)
  - ARB-3457 Rego Sportswear Mfg. Co., 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 69)
  - ARB-3460 G. & M. Mfg. Company, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 70)
  - ARB-3462 Giant Penny, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 71)
  - ARB-3464 Joselynn Embroidery Co., Inc., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 72)
  - ARB-3465 Pace's Physiognomical Ladies Haircutting Salon, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 73)
  - ARB-3466 Union News Company, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 74)
  - ARB-3467 Pioneer Mounting & Finishing, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 75)
  - ARB-3468 Century Products Works, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 76)
  - ARB-3469 - ARB-3474 Modern Handcraft Importing Co. et al., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 77)
  - ARB-3475 - ARB-3485 Jack Silverman et al, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 78)
  - ARB-3486 Otis Elevator, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 79)
  - ARB-3487 274 East 93 Street - Brooklyn, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 80)
  - ARB-3488 574 St. Nicholas Avenue, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 81)
  - ARB-3489 Paragon Paint & Varnish Corp., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 82)
  - ARB-3490 R.D. Sickler Co., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 83)
  - ARB-3491 Greer Hydraulics, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 84)
  - ARB-3492 Lincoln Metal Prod. Corp., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 85)
  - ARB-3493 Union News Company, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 86)
  - ARB-3494 Industrial Acoustics Co., Inc., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 87)
  - ARB-3495 specialty Assembling & Packing Co., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 88)
  - ARB-3496 11 West Prospect Avenue, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 89)
  - ARB-3497 257 Valentine Lane, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 90)
  - ARB-3498 1124 Stratford Ave., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 91)
  - ARB-3499 2406 University Ave., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 92)
  - ARB-3500 Christensen & Weiss, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 93)
  - ARB-3501 Zimets Bed Spring Corp., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 94)
  - ARB-3502 Kendor Oldsmobile, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 95)
  - ARB-3503 Robin Pharmacal Corporation, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 96)
  - ARB-3504 Tip Toe Inn, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 97)
  - ARB-3505 239 West 145th Street, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 98)
  - ARB-3506 137 West 137th Street, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 99)
  - ARB-3507 39-45 East 9th Street 40-50 East 10th Street, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 100)
  - ARB-3509 A & M Carting, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 101)
  - ARB-3508 - ARB-3528 A & B Trucking et al., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 102)
  - ARB-3513 D & B Carting Co., 1957 (Box 80, Folder 103)
  - ARB-3518 Louis Genovese, 1956-1957 (Box 80, Folder 104)
- ARB 3529 - ARB 3685 (1957). (Box 81)
  - ARB-3529 Goerz Optical Company, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - ARB-3530 Louis Sabel, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - ARB-3531 Hill's Supermarkets, Inc., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - ARB-3532 Brenner Metal Products Corp., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - ARB-3533 Herbert J. Caplan, Inc., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - ARB-3534 Electronic Devices, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - ARB-3535 David Sarkin, Inc., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - ARB-3536 Skalet Jewelry Mfg. Inc., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - ARB-3537 Little Toodle Bake Shop, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - ARB-3538 Alpine Wine & Liquor Corp., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - ARB-3539 927-931 Faile Street, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - ARB-3540 Atlantic Yeast, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - ARB-3541 - ARB-3542 N.A. Aristocraft Baby Carriage Co. Jersey Furniture Frame Co., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - ARB-3543 Barney's Interior Decorators, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - ARB-3544 Fordham Window Cleaning, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - ARB-3545 N. K. Window Cleaning, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - ARB-3546 Erickson Pre-Cast Construction Co., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - ARB-3547 Perma Plating, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - ARB-3548 Jolan Mfg. Co., Inc., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - ARB-3549 Waldman's Men's Shop, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - ARB-3550 Amp Auto Service, Inc., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - ARB-3551 Engel Furniture Company, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - ARB-3552 Champion Envelope Co., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - ARB-3553 Williams Sportswear, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - ARB-3554 2798 8th Avenue, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - ARB-3555 Acme Chain Co., Inc., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - ARB-3556 511 West 235th Street, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - ARB-3557 555 East Tremont Ave., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 28)
  - ARB-3558 889 St. Nicholas Ave., 1959 (Box 81, Folder 29)
  - ARB-3559 Figge & Hutwelker Company, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 30)
  - ARB-3560 Goldman Super Market, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 31)
  - ARB-3561 Everlast Metal Products Corp., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 32)
  - ARB-3562 Flight Foods Inc., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 33)
  - ARB-3563 Fuchs Bros. Sewing Machine, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 34)
  - ARB-3564 505 West 164th Street, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 35)
  - ARB-3565 Able Steel Partition, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 36)
  - ARB-3566 C. R. A., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 37)
  - ARB-3567 Ernst Slide Fastener, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 38)
  - ARB-3568 Optical Products Corporation, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 39)
  - ARB-3569 Penn-Akron Hardware, Inc., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 40)
  - ARB-3570 Haller Plastics, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 41)
  - ARB-3571 Packer Industrial Finishing Co., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 42)
  - ARB-3572 Rockaway Cabinets Company, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 43)
  - ARB-3573 Rexart Metal Industries, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 44)
  - ARB-3574 Up To Date Candy Company, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 45)
  - ARB-3575 545 West 236th Street, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 46)
  - ARB-3576 1280 Walton Avenue, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 47)
  - ARB-3577 Embassy Grocery, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 48)
  - ARB-3578 - ARB-3580 A & J Rubbish Carting et al., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 49)
  - ARB-3581 - ARB-3583 McClellan Upholstery et al., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 50)
  - ARB-3584 Sharodan Furniture Co., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 51)
  - ARB-3585 City Hall Hardware, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 52)
  - ARB-3586 Duvernoy & Sons Inc., 1957-1959 (Box 81, Folder 53)
  - ARB-3587 Reliable Machine Works, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 54)
  - ARB-3588 Risbergs Building Materials Corp., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 55)
  - ARB-3589 thru ARB-3593 Budd Looms et al., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 56)
  - ARB-3594 Service Manufacturing Co., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 57)
  - ARB-3594 50 East 196th Street, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 58)
  - ARB-3596 - ARB-3597 Everbest Furniture Co. Kon-Tempo Furniture Co., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 59)
  - ARB-3598 Modern Handcraft Importing Inc., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 60)
  - ARB-3599 H.L. Gross, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 61)
  - ARB-3600 Herman Bellman Baking Company, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 62)
  - ARB-3601 Sutter Auto Funeral Service Inc., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 63)
  - ARB-3602 3505 Rochambeau Avenue, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 64)
  - ARB-3603 Red Coach Grill, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 65)
  - ARB-3604 U.S. Trucking Corp., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 66)
  - ARB-3605 509 West 212 Street, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 67)
  - ARB-3606 - ARB-3618 Airway's Restaurant et al., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 68)
  - ARB-3619 Herman-Bellman Co., Inc., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 69)
  - ARB-3620 Associated Amusement Machine Operators of N.Y., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 70)
  - ARB-3621 Queens Boulevard Gardens, Inc., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 71)
  - ARB-3622 Anchor Cleaning Service, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 72)
  - ARB-3623 Linder Oldsmobile, Inc., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 73)
  - ARB-3624 Firsch & Company, Inc., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 74)
  - ARB-3625 Miller Art Company, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 75)
  - ARB-3626 Drake Bakeries, Inc., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 76)
  - ARB-3627 Wilson Specialties Co., Inc., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 77)
  - ARB-3628 Farmers Produce (L.H. Burns Inc.), 1957 (Box 81, Folder 78)
  - ARB-3629 American Gun Handle Corp., 1957 (Box 81, Folder 79)
  - ARB-3630 Independent Fireproof Door, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 80)
  - ARB-3631 Unique Optical Company, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 81)
  - ARB-3632 751 East 168th Street, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 82)